epractizelabs.com 2008-12-18

# EPractize Labs Software - License Agreement, Privacy Policy, Trade Marks

EPractize Labs respects the privacy of the users. 

**Personal Information**

Registration is not required for visitors to the site who do not require any specific services. 

There are some activities like license request and customer support, where providing your Personal Information is required. EPractize Labs ensures that personally identifiable information of individual users will not be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties. 

However, EPractize Labs may use the registration and other information voluntarily submitted in the following ways: 

  * To provide our R&D team with the information that is useful in enhancing and providing new features and services for EPractize Labs users. 
  * To provide our selective partner with few information for value-added offerings. 
  * EPractize Labs sometimes permit third parties to offer subscription and/or registration-based the contents provided by any organization towards the Advanced Edition will be maintained as Confidential. We shall not share the contents with any other organization, individuals or our customer's services through EPractize Labs. In this event, EPractize Labs is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties and users should check the applicable privacy policy of such party before providing personally identifiable information. 
  * To allow us to potentially vary advertising according to user preference. EPractize Labs reserves the right to analyze and report behavior and characteristics of the user in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the site and to inform advertisers of such information. 

**Resume Collection**

The Site provides a capability for users to submit their resumes to EPractize Labs via email. Any resume received by EPractize Labs will be held in confidence and used only for the purpose of considering the submitting party for employment. Such information is not shared with the third parties. 

**No use of "Cookies"**

EPractize Labs does not currently use Cookies on this Site. 

**E-mail information**

When we receive e-mails from you, we may retain the content of any e-mail messages sent to us, as well as details of your e-mail address. 

**Contact**

If you have any questions about this Site, please email the webmaster at [webmaster@epractizelabs.com](mailto:webmaster@epractizelabs.com)
